A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of the Medical Letter publication, 1986-1995 FA1103
Rockefeller Archive Center
- TML, 36-11 - Cisapride for nocturnal heartburn, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 36-11 - Cisapride for nocturnal heartburn, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 36-13 - Extended-release isosorbide mononitritate for angina, 1994 February 4 (Box 92, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 36-15 - Terazosin for benign prostatic hyperplasia, 1994 February 18 (Box 92, Folder 6-9)
- TML, 36-19 - Drugs for treatment of acute otitis media in children, 1994 March 4 (Box 92, Folder 10-15)
- TML, 36-21 - Intrathecal baclofen for spasticity, 1994 March 4 (Box 92, Folder 16-18)
- TML, 36-23 - Ziac for hypertension, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 19-20)
- TML, 36-23 - Ziac for hypertension, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- TML, 36-24 - Oral transmucosal fentanyl citrate, 1994 March 18 (Box 93, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 36-27 - Drugs for non-HIV viral infections, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 4-10)
- TML, 36-33 - Risperidone for chronic schizophrenia, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 36-34 - Aerosolized deoxyribonuclease for cystic fibrosis, 1994 April 15 (Box 93, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 36-35 - Opthalmic levocabastine for allergic conjunctivitis, 1994 April 15 (Box 93, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 36-37 - Salmeterol, 1994 April 29 (Box 94, Folder 1-6)
- TML, 36-39 - Gabapentin - a new anticonvulsant, 1994 April 29 (Box 94, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 36-41 - Advice for travelers, 1994 May 13 (Box 94, Folder 10-14)
- TML, 36-45 - Fluvastatin for lowering cholesterol, 1994 May 27 (Box 94, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 36-46 - Captopril for diabetic nephropathy, 1994 May 27 (Box 94, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 36-46 - Captopril for diabetic nephropathy, 1994 May 27 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- TML, 36-50 - Aprotinin to decrease bleeding in cardiac surgery, 1994 June 10 (Box 95, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 36-52 - LAAM - a long-acting methadone for treatment of heroin addiction, 1994 June 10 (Box 95, Folder 5-7)
- TML, 36-53 - The choice of antibacterial drugs, 1994 June 24 (Box 95, Folder 8-15)
- TML, 36-61 - Granisetron to prevent vomiting after cancer chemotherapy, 1994 July 8 (Box 95, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 36-61 - Granisetron to prevent vomiting after cancer chemotherapy, 1994 July 8 (Box 96, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 36-65 - Drugs for treatment of peptic ulcers, 1994 July 22 (Box 96, Folder 3-7)
- TML, 36-68 - Ketoconazole shampoo for dandruff, 1994 July 22 (Box 96, Folder 8-10)
- TML, 36-69 - An ACE inhibitor after a myocardial infarction, 1994 August 5 (Box 96, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 36-70 - Calcipotriene for psoraisis, 1994 August 5 (Box 96, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 36-71 - Rocuronium - a new neuromuscular blocker, 1994 August 5 (Box 96, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 36-73 - Torsemide (Demadex) - a new loop diuretic, 1994 August 19 (Box 97, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 36-74 - Valproate for bipolar disorder, 1994 August 19 (Box 97, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 36-76 - Oral pilocarpine of xerostomia, 1994 August 19 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- TML, 36-77 - Recombinant human growth hormone, 1994 September 2 (Box 97, Folder 7-8)
- TML, 36-78 - Acrivastatine-Pseudoephedrine (Semprex-D) for seasonal allergic rhinitis, 1994 September 2 (Box 97, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 36-81 - Oral fluconazole for vaginal candidiasis, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 36-82 - Tacrolimus (FK506) for organ transplants, 1994 September 16 (Box 97, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 36-84 - Influenza vaccine, 1994-1995 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- TML, 36-85 - Home testing of cholesterol, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 2-3)
- TML, 36-86 - Inplantable cardioverter (defibrillators), 1994 September 30 (Box 98, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 36-89 - Drugs for psychiatric disorders, 1994 October 14 (Box 98, Folder 8-13)
- TML, 36-97 - Famciclovir for herpes zoster, 1994 October 28 (Box 98, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 36-99 - Doxepin cream for pruritus, 1994 October 28 (Box 98, Folder 17)
- TML - Breathe Right Strips to Stop Snoring, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 36-107 - Fluoxetine (Prozac) and other drugs for treatment of obesity, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 3-6)
- TML, 36-107 - Fluoxetine (Prozac) and other drugs for treatment of obesity, 1994 (Box 99, Folder 12-15)
- TML, 36-101 - Drugs for rheumatoid arthritis, 1994 November 11 (Box 99, Folder 7-11)
- TML, 36-109 - Adderal and other drugs for Attention-Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD), 1994 November 25 (Box 99, Folder 16-17)
- TML, 36-109 - Adderal and other drugs for Attention-Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD), 1994 November 25 (Box 100, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 36-110 - A reminder - Piperacillin (Tazobactam) is not for Pseudomonas, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 4)
- TML, 36-111 - Drugs for stable angina pectoris, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 5-10)
- TML, 36-115 - Yohimbine for male sexual dysfunction, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 11-14)
- TML, 36-116 - Treatment of hypothermia, 1994 December 23 (Box 100, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 36-118 - Cysteamine for cystinosis, 1994 December 23 (Box 100, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 36-16 - Systemic antifungal drugs, 1994 February 18 (Box 101, Folder 1-6)
- TML, 36-49 - Venlafaxine - a new antidepressant, 1994 June 10 (Box 101, Folder 7-9)
- TML, 36-63 - Intranasal budesonide for allergic rhinitis, 1994 July 8 (Box 101, Folder 10-12)
- TML - Special Publications - Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 13-14)
- TML - Special Publications - Handbook of Antimicrobial Therapy - Adverse Effects, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- TML, 37-53 - Estrogen-Progestin combination for postmenopausal use, 1995 June 9 (Box 102, Folder 1-3)
  Restricted material - Open in 2021
- TML, 37-55 - Varicella vaccine, 1995 June 23 (Box 102, Folder 4-7)
- TML, 37-57 - Losartan for hypertension, 1995 June 23 (Box 102, Folder 8-11)
- TML, 37-72 - Vinorelbine for treatment of advanced non-small-cell lung cancer, 1995 August 18 (Box 102, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 37-110 - Dexrazoxane for cardiac protection against doxorubicin, 1995 November 24 (Box 102, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 37-115 - Dalteparin, 1995 December 8 (Box 102, Folder 18-20)
- TML, 37-5 - Fluticasone propionate nasal spray for allergic rhinitis, 1995 January 20 (Box 103, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 37-9 - Choice of Contraceptives, 1995 February 3 (Box 103, Folder 4-9)
- TML, 37-24 - Portable Prothrombin Time Monitors, 1995 March 17 (Box 103, Folder 10-11)
- TML, 37-37 - Drugs for epilepsy, 1995 April 28 (Box 103, Folder 12-14)
- TML - Carvedilol, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 15-16)
- TML, 37-76 - Dorzolamide - A topical carbonic anydrase inhibator for glaucoma, 1995 September 1 (Box 103, Folder 17-18)
- TML, 37-76 - Dorzolamide - A topical carbonic anydrase inhibator for glaucoma, 1995 September 1 (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 37-1 - Drugs for Asthma, 1995 January 6 (Box 104, Folder 3-9)
- TML, 37-25 - Drugs of choice for cancer chemotherapy, 1995 March 31 (Box 104, Folder 10-16)
- TML, 37-14 - Aspirin for prevention of myocardial infarction, 1995 February 17 (Box 105, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 37-79 - Antimicrobial prophylaxis in surgery, 1995 September 15 (Box 105, Folder 4-8)
- TML, 37-114 - Amiodarone IV - Intravenous Amiodarone, 1995 December 8 (Box 105, Folder 9-11)
- TML, 37-52 - Abciximab to prevent vessel closure after angioplasty, 1995 June 9 (Box 105, Folder 12-14)
- TML, 37-83 - Intravenous injection of alprostadil for erectile dysfunction, 1995 September 29 (Box 105, Folder 15-17)
- TML, 37-97 - Nalmefene a long acting injectable, 1995 October 27 (Box 105, Folder 18-19)
- TML, 37-60 - Organ donation for transplantation, 1995 July 7 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- TML, 37-60 - Organ donation for transplantation, 1995 July 7 (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 37-23 - Pegaspargase for acute lymphoblastic leukemia, 1995 March 17 (Box 106, Folder 3-4)
- TML, 37-87 - Drugs for AIDS and associated infections, 1995 October 13 (Box 106, Folder 5-17)
- TML, 37-87 - Drugs for AIDS and associated infections, 1995 October 13 (Box 107, Folder 1-3)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 4-5)
- TML, 37-43 - Treatment of nerve gas poisoning, 1995 May 12 (Box 107, Folder 6-8)
- TML, 37-35 - Drugs that cause photosensitivity, 1995 April 14 (Box 107, Folder 9-12)
- TML - Vinorelbine Reprints, 1995 (Box 107, Folder 13-16)
- TML, 36-48 - EDTA cheleation therapy for atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease, 1994 May 27 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- TML, 36-7 - Piperaillin-Tazobactam, 1994 January 21 (Box 108, Folder 1-4)
- TML, 37-51 - Hepatitis A vaccine, 1995 June 9 (Box 108, Folder 5-8)
- TML, 37-45 - Drugs for Hypertension, 1995 May 26 (Box 108, Folder 9-14)
- TML, 37-63 - Lansoprazole, 1995 July 21 (Box 108, Folder 15-18)
- TML, 36-26 - Lodoxamide for vernal keratoconjunctivitis, 1994 March 18 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- TML, 37-21 - Lamotrigine for epilepsy, 1995 March 17 (Box 109, Folder 1-5)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Parkinson's Disease, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 6-9)
- TML - Epilepsy Reprints, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 10-13)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Cholesterol Lowering, 1995 (Box 109, Folder 14-19)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Cholesterol-Lowering, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 37-111 - Melatonin, 1995 November 24 (Box 110, Folder 4-6)
- TML - Special Publications - Drugs of Choice - Congestive Heart Failure, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 7-10)
- TML, 37-41 - Metformin for non-insulin dependent diabetes mellitus, 1995 May 12 (Box 110, Folder 11-13)
- TML, 37-71 - Peripheral blood stem cell transplantation, 1995 August 18 (Box 110, Folder 14-16)
- TML, 37-96 - Sevoflurane for general anesthesia, 1995 October 27 (Box 110, Folder 17-19)
- TML, 37-113 - Riluzole for amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, 1995 December 8 (Box 111, Folder 1-2)
- TML, 37-33 - Nefazodone for depression, 1995 April 14 (Box 111, Folder 3-5)
- TML, 37-17 - Drugs for Migraine, 1995 March 3 (Box 111, Folder 6-12)
- TML, 37-67 - Drugs for Tuberculosis, 1995 August 4 (Box 111, Folder 13-17)
- TML, 37-59 - Tramadol - a new oral analgesic, 1995 July 7 (Box 111, Folder 18-21)
- TML, 37-75 - Moexipril - another ACE inhibitor for hypertension, 1995 September 1 (Box 112, Folder 1-3)
- TML, 37-64 - Naltrexone for alcohol dependence, 1995 July 21 (Box 112, Folder 4-6)
- TML, 37-99 - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1995 November 10 (Box 112, Folder 7-16)
- TML, 37-99 - Drugs for parasitic infections, 1995 November 10 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- TML - Mycophenolate mofetia - a new immunosuppressant for organ transplants, 1995 September 29 (Box 113, Folder 2-4)
- TML, 37-6 - Smoking Cessation - Use of Nicotine to stop smoking, 1995 January 20 (Box 113, Folder 5-10)
- TML, 37-117 - Drugs for sexually transmitted diseases, 1995 December 22 (Box 113, Folder 11-18)